Please wait for the game to commence.
Five minutes until registration closes.
It's a Ferris wheel this time?
What game could it be?
Our visas are expiring tonight.
We have no choice but to join.
Do you guys have a minute?
Have you ever heard of "the Beach"?
What?
- Ignore him. Let's go!
- Wait!
Just where is the Beach?
Registration has closed.
We can't seem to find the Beach anywhere.
We are back here again.
If we don't participate in a game soon,
our visas will expire.
My visa will only last
for another three days.
I have three days
to find out where the Beach is
and put an end to this ridiculous game.
Are you really going to hunt with me
in the morning?
Is that all right?
I'll try my best not to stand in your way.
What you've learned
while living in nature,
I want to pick up those skills too
while there's still time.
There's a limit to our lives.
I've lived my life so far
without thinking about that.
Those guys.
They died believing in me.
I may also die in the near future.
For now,
I don't want to waste
even a single minute or second!
Good night.
When there are no lights in the city,
the stars look really beautiful.
That hurts!
Itchy.
It's so itchy.
That's why I told you
it's impossible to sleep outside.
Just come inside the tent already.
What?
But…
It's important to have sufficient sleep.
If you can't even take care of yourself,
you might die anytime here.
This is a mud puddle.
Boars clean themselves here.
What's more,
you can see the ground they dug
to eat leaf buds
as well as the marks they left
while sharpening their fangs.
There are boars in Odaiba?
There's no one left in the cities,
so the animals came in.
Looking at footprints
is a basic hunting technique.
The habitat of beasts
expands out like mesh.
What you need in hunting
is the ability to connect these mesh lines
and understand
the movements of these animals.
So we shouldn't just focus on one thing.
We need to consider the big picture.
- You learn fast.
- I fought the same way in Battleland.
Battleland?
Oh, it's an online game.
Online game?
Games you play online.
How is it?
There are
around ten participants, I think.
There are some who have formed teams, too.
What about your side?
There are four people here.
I'll talk to them and pretend I'm joining.
Wait, Usagi!
- What's the matter?
- Look at the participants' wrists.
- Wrists?
- Is there anyone wearing a locker key?
The ones that you usually see in gyms.
If I remember, during our tag game…
I got it.
Those with the keys are a team.
From where I'm standing,
there are two of them!
Take note of those two.
Understood.
Those who cleared the game
left the building.
I knew it!
They're all wearing locker keys.
There are three people left in my area.
They are leaving.
The two with the locker keys
seem to be a pair.
They're going back to the same area.
I'll follow them!
All right, we did it!
Let's head back!
Usagi.
Do you see it too, Arisu?
I'm sure of it. It's those guys!
There's a car.
They may be collecting these cars
systematically.
They're on the move!
Same over here!
The car is moving towards Maihama!
This side, too!
Is that the place?
BEACH
"The Beach."
That's the place!
How do they have electricity?
Will we find the answers
to our questions there?
Good morning.
I'm sorry that we were so rough.
We heard that there were some people
sneaking around the place.
What are your motives?
We heard that we'll know the answer…
if we come here.
What this game is about
and where all the people
who disappeared went.
Exactly.
We know the answers
to the questions you both have.
Welcome
to the Beach, the utopia.
This…
is the answer.
I'll tell you the truth.
There's only one way
to end this hellish nightmare.
We clear the games
and collect all the playing cards.
All the playing cards?
So if we gather all of them,
will the original world return?
The original world will not return.
Only one person
can return to the original world.
Only one person?
It's impossible for a single person
to clear all the games
and gather all 52 playing cards.
You can't leave this country
by working alone.
That's why everyone unites as one
in order to let that one person
leave the country.
This is the Beach's objective.
I've heard that the two of you
possess good cards.
I'll have both of you play your part
and help us gather the remaining cards.
And if we refuse?
You can't reject me.
Your visa is expiring today.
You have no choice
but to participate in a game, don't you?
We can return if we gather all the cards.
Is that really true?
I can't reveal everything yet,
but I have a credible source
for that information.
Before both of you entered this world,
we already thoroughly investigated
everything about this country.
You've been referring to this place
as a "country."
The fact that we've been issued visas
means that this is a country.
The people in Tokyo didn't just disappear.
It's hypothesized that we've entered
another country accidentally.
If that's true,
then there must be a way to return.
And we created an organization here.
Fuels are used to generate electricity,
and rainwater is used as a water supply.
We have even secured firearms
around the country.
However, only a selected few
are allowed to use them.
Our objective is to unite
and collect all the playing cards.
And…
there are only three rules
in this utopian Beach.
Rule number one. You must
always wear swimsuits at the Beach.
What?
You can't hide firearms in a swimsuit.
Safe, isn't it?
You're free to drink,
take drugs, or even have sex!
Feel free
to enjoy your life to the fullest.
We damaged all the door locks
with super glue.
No one is allowed to hide anything!
Rule number two.
All playing cards belong to the Beach.
We will take away all the cards
the two of you possess.
Those that have contributed more cards
will be promoted to a higher number.
After everyone works together
to get the first person out the country,
if we gather enough duplicated cards,
we will soon be able to have the second
or even the third person
to leave this country.
The day will come when everyone
at the Beach will be able to leave!
And when will that be?
What if…
I reject your offer?
Rule number three of the Beach.
This is the last rule.
Death to the traitors.
Everyone at the Beach vowed
to produce the first departure
from this country
at the cost of our lives.
It's our mission, our duty!
Those who show contempt for that…
will never be forgiven by the Beach.
Usagi.
I'm sorry.
I dragged you into this.
Don't apologize.
I wasn't dragged into this.
This is a path that I chose.
It's the Seven of Hearts!
Luck is on our side.
Now we're another step closer
to departure!
Thank you!
We will consider promoting both of you
to a higher rank number.
Well then,
please enjoy your stay at the Beach!
What the hell is this?
Somehow,
it feels like we're being watched.
Newcomers are always
a spectacle to others.
This is the Beach's Special Time!
This is completely
an escape from reality.
It's time for the games!
A new game arena
has been located in the Shinagawa ward!
- The cars are in the second parking lot!
- Adachi and Koto wards, form two groups!
- Hatter!
My comrades!
The time has come again tonight.
Do not falter!
This is a war against fear!
Everyone here has the courage
to overcome their obstacles.
Everyone here
is now one!
We shall unite and gather all cards
and return to the original world together!
And…
that day is upon us!
Let's go!
Get in the car marked with your number!
So we're just an army
to collect the cards, huh?
We've been divided into separate games.
You must survive.
What's the matter?
I was in the same game as them.
The two of them?
Yes.
They might be useful.
To our plan, that is.
Teams 1 to 9 will head
to the Shinagawa ward,
while Teams 10 to 17
will head to the Koto ward.
Teams 18 to 24 will…
Game, "Beast Hunter."
Using this scoreboard as a reference,
please cooperate and defeat
the beasts in the area together.
Game, "Hunting Competition."
Game, "Human Elevator."
Game, "Bingo in Match Factory."
You only have nine matches.
Answer all the numbers
you find across the 24 rooms
and clear the game by achieving bingo.
It's the militants!
50 POINTS RECEIVED
30 POINTS RECEIVED
Just where the hell is it?
Where is it hiding?
ONE POINT RECEIVED
Piece of cake!
Here it is!
Room 4D is nine!
PLAYERS
ONE PER PERSON
This is a trial to see if you're fit to be
an executive member of Beach.
Well, do your best.
A waterproof case?
I'm Kuina. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Ann!
Water is starting to spurt out,
and it's filling up the area!
Hey, you're…
You're the one from the tag game.
So you're alive.
Yes, I help with maintenance
at the Beach and--
Leave the formalities for after the game.
What's with this room?
Registration has closed.
There are currently seven participants.
The game will now commence.
Difficulty, Four of Diamonds.
The last Diamond card we need.
Game, "Light Bulb."
"Light bulb"?
OPEN AND CLOSE FREELY
Question.
Which switch turns on the light bulb?
WHICH SWITCH TURNS ON THE LIGHT BULB?
Rule number one.
Only one switch among A, B, and C
will turn on the light bulb.
Rule number two.
You only have one chance
to flip a switch while the door is open.
OPEN AND CLOSE FREELY
If the door is closed, you can flip
the switches as much as you like.
Rule number three.
If someone is in the room,
or if a switch has been turned on,
the door will be locked in place
and cannot be moved.
You only have one chance
to answer as a group.
If you answer correctly
which switch turns on the light bulb,
you clear the game.
If the water level rises and touches
the electrical wires, it's game over.
Electrical wires?
You'll get electrocuted!
Is that what they meant?
The water level is slowly rising!
If it rises too high, everyone dies.
Anyway, we just need to figure out
the switch for the light bulb, right?
I'll head into that room first,
so let's take turns!
If you enter, the door won't close!
Let's see…
So we only have one chance
to turn on the switch with the door open.
But there's no point in flipping
the switches when the door is closed!
For example, if you turn on Switch A
with the door open
and it doesn't light up,
then the answer is not A.
And why is that wrong?
Anyway, let's just flip Switch A
with the door open--
What if your answer is wrong?
If it turns on, it's A.
If it doesn't, it's either B or C.
- At least we have a 50 percent chance!
- It's 66 percent.
Shouldn't it be 50 percent?
I don't understand it at all.
What will you do, Arisu?
But there's no other choice.
For now, let's turn on a switch
with the door open!
If the bulb doesn't turn on,
we'll decide on one out of the two!
Are you just going to guess?
- We have no choice but to bet on it.
- Using all seven lives here?
Or six, I guess.
Yes. If you know the answer,
then do it already!
Didn't I tell you?
I'm testing you.
Don't drag us into the newcomer's trial!
Giving up already?
I give up! Please tell us the answer!
This is really bad!
Ann!
Arisu, just do it.
It's going to be too late!
I'm doing it then!
Are you really all right with that?
Just do it already!
What are you waiting for?
You only have one chance
to flip a switch while the door is open.
For example, if you turn on Switch A
with the door open
and it doesn't light up,
then the answer is not A.
If it turns on, it's A.
If it doesn't, it's either B or C.
If the door is closed, you can flip
the switches as much as you like.
Let's close the door.
What?
Close the door! Hurry up!
If you don't do as Arisu says,
everyone will die!
Stay like this!
- What are you up to?
- I hope you know what you're doing!
Hurry up!
Open the door!
Hurry up.
It didn't turn on!
Kuina, touch the bulb!
- What?
- Just go! We're running out of time.
Please!
That's hot!
- The answer is A--
- Switch A!
Game cleared. Congratulations.
Electricity generates heat.
If the bulb had been on,
it would feel hot.
If not, it would have felt cold.
And we only had one chance
to check with our own eyes.
With this, the chance of survival was
increased from 66 to 100 percent.
It's 50 percent, right?
I don't care anymore.
You survived.
Yes.
She knew the answer.
Ann was trying to test me.
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
Your girlfriend?
What?
You're wrong!
You guys get along,
so why not date each other?
You never know when you're going to die.
What are you saying?
There are things you should do
while you're still alive!
My mom is sick in the hospital.
She can't even relieve herself
without my help,
and yet I had to be separated from her.
So I want to return alive.
That's why I quit smoking.
I haven't been able to quit before this.
I'll need some stamina
in order to survive, right?
I'll definitely survive
and return to the original world.
Hey, stop playing that tacky music!
It's the militants at the Beach.
If you want
to live peacefully at the Beach,
avoid getting involved with them.
The leader, Aguni, is an ex-SDF officer,
and he is in charge of
all the weapons at the Beach.
The ones currently in power at the Beach
are the Number One, Hatter,
and his devotees
as well as the militants led by Aguni.
We've only barely managed
to maintain peace and order here,
but a conflict between the two parties
could happen anytime.
What happened to your pal?
I see. He died.
What a shame.
So only the small fish survived.
Do you know each other?
You,
bring that woman over.
Yes.
- Hey!
- Stop. Don't get yourself involved!
Our boss says
he wants to have a taste of you.
Come.
Stop it.
What should we do about this kid?
Break his legs
so that he'll die in the next game.
Yes. You guys!
Bring the woman to him.
You come with me.
Stand up.
Is this a fight?
Back off, Hatter.
This doesn't concern you.
I can't do that.
As the Number One, I'm obliged
to maintain order at the Beach.
Could you let off the newcomers
on my account, Aguni?
Niragi.
I only take orders from the boss.
Then let me ask your boss.
Who is your boss,
Aguni?
It's you, right?
Go take a shower.
All executive members are to gather
in the meeting room!
Arisu, you're coming too.
I've heard about your potential from Ann.
Follow me.
I'll be back.
So what do you think about him?
I like him.
- We still have four missing.
- We're starting the meeting!
Those who have nothing to do here, leave.
It's you.
Two of Spades.
Six of Spades. Four of Diamonds.
Two of Clubs.
We've collected all four of them.
Until now, we still haven't found
any face cards.
If face cards do not exist,
then we're only left with Ten of Hearts.
Ten of Hearts.
It has never appeared in a game before.
If it doesn't appear, we can't clear it.
Maybe there needs
to be a condition for it to appear.
Maybe it is not in Tokyo.
A game arena has never been found
outside of Tokyo.
- But we haven't investigated that far yet.
- The strategy won't change.
We will continue investigating
the game arenas in town.
Make sure you have days left on your visas
and keep a lookout for the Ten of Hearts.
I need to replenish my visa soon.
There's a way to earn visa days for sure.
Is that so?
Heart games let you toy
with the hearts and feelings of others.
If you bring along those
that don't mind dying,
you'll survive for sure.
Even in the Seven of Hearts game
that Arisu cleared.
The same thing happened, didn't it?
It's a game that doesn't
even require you to use your brain!
As someone who cleared a Hearts game,
do you have any advice for us, Arisu?
But would a Hearts game
appear so conveniently?
On top of that, we won't know what type
of game it is until registration closes.
But we should be able to deduce it
based on the probability theory.
I don't need
such a pretentious investigation method.
I'll join the next game.
Be it Hearts or Spades.
Someone like me with a 100 percent
winning rate will clear it easily!
I'll join the games
until the Ten of Hearts card appears!
The day where we gather all cards
and depart from this country is near!
Executive members, I'm counting on
you guys to oversee things here.
The meeting is adjourned!
You should drink too, Arisu.
I also like to enjoy myself before a game.
There's no poison in it!
It seems like you don't trust me.
I like your prudence.
What did you do in the original world?
Nothing.
So you're a NEET?
I ran a host club in Kabukicho.
It's called Beach.
Have you heard of it?
It was quite famous, you know?
Beach, Beach, there's no sand
But it's the utopia Beach
It was advertised all over Tokyo
on cars with loudspeakers, you know?
All I did was play games at home.
Did you know?
I wanted to be the best in Kabukicho…
desperately.
My subordinates all looked up to me,
and I told them I'll do
whatever it takes to rule over this place!
As a host,
it's all over if you're looked down on
by your customers.
No matter how much you're made to drink…
you must never lose your human pride.
I instilled that mindset
into my subordinates.
However…
that pushed him over the edge.
In the dormitory,
he hanged himself.
Everyone.
They all left me.
I…
I wanted to rule the place with them.
Now that I think about it,
his death was a necessary evil.
In order for me to mature.
Mature?
In this new Beach,
all the players will devote
their bodies and lives to me!
And I will be a hero.
The one and only hero
to succeed in leaving this country!
And that is me, Hatter.
For a hero,
tragedies are needed.
To the second Beach.
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu